rncdn3.com 2016-04-04

# Privacy Policy

Reflected Networks, Inc. Privacy Policy

This Customer Privacy Policy of Reflected Networks, Inc. covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Reflected any time you interact with Reflected, such as when you visit Reflected’s web site, when you purchase Reflected’s products and services, or when you call or e-mail Reflected’s sales or support staff. Please take a moment to carefully read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Reflected, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

1\. Reasons Reflected Collects Personal Information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver excellent customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.  If you do not want Reflected to keep you up to date with our news and the latest information on products and services please email [Privacy@Reflected.net](mailto:Privacy@Reflected.net).

2\. Information Reflected Collects and How the Information May be Used

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help Reflected give you better products and Services. For example:

  * We may ask for or obtain your personal information from our online portal, in connection with your purchase of our products or services, or when you’re dealing with a service issue on the phone, via e-mail, or through our portal. 

  * When you interact with Reflected, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; information about Reflected’s products and services you utilize, and information relating to a support or service issue. 

  * We collect information regarding customer activities on our web sites, including through our online portals. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our web sites, products, and services are of most interest to them. 

  * We may use personal information to provide products and services that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve our products and services. 

This information may be shared with third parties or in special circumstances as described elsewhere in this policy.

3\. Your Online Reflected ID and Related Information

Our web sites (including our on line portals) allow you to create a Reflected ID based on your personal information. This convenient service allows for easier use of our web services. In order to create your Reflected ID or use our online portal, you will need to create a profile by providing information including name, phone number, email address, and in some cases mailing address. The system saves the information through the online portal which you can use and edit when performing various activities relating to our web site (including our on line portals) and the products and services you purchase from Reflected.

4\. Publicly Displayed Information is Public

If you use a Reflected chat room you should be aware that any information you share is potentially visible to other individuals within Reflected and your company. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these chat rooms can be read, collected, or used by Reflected and other individuals within your company. Reflected is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these chats. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously nonpublic, available, Reflected will collect that information from your interaction.

5\. When Reflected Discloses Your Information

Reflected takes your privacy very seriously. Reflected does not sell or license your contact information to advertisers or marketers.

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within our corporate group globally as well as our third party service providers who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with our privacy policy. 

There are also times when it may be advantageous for Reflected to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Reflected has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Reflected to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products or render services to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, or conduct customer research. In such situation these companies are prohibited from using your personal information for any unauthorized purposes and are also obligated to protect your information in accordance with the Reflected’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive services, receive customer service, or access certain services, offers, and content on our web site.

Reflected may take the personal information we receive from individuals responding to our customer surveys or other information gathering efforts in connection with our customer support, online portals and other services and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers we may have, to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions or otherwise use such information to improve the quality of its services to our customer, and to modify or develop new services and products.

We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, litigation or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information. We may also disclose personal information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our contracts, policies and procedures. Finally we may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

6\. How Reflected Protects Your Personal Information

Reflected takes precautions—including administrative, technical, and physical measures—to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Our web sites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required and to make online purchases you must use an SSL-enabled browser in order to protect the confidentiality of your information while it’s transmitted over the Internet. You should also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser.

While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining your personal information.

7\. Integrity of Your Personal Information

Reflected has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. You always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided and can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date through your online portal or via e-mail at [privacy@Reflected.net](mailto:privacy@Reflected.net). In addition, you can obtain a copy of your personal information, your service history, and your interactions with support staff through the online portal.

8\. No Age Verification

Reflected does not verify the age of any customer or individual accessing Reflected’s web sites (including online portals).  Reflected recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products or services where minors may access such products or services, including via our online portal. We do not verify the age of individuals having access to our portals or web sites, although we do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of majority (in each relevant jurisdiction) for marketing purposes or otherwise. Notwithstanding the foregoing, it is Reflected’s policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. 

9\. Cookies and Other Technologies

While Reflected’s web sites do not presently use “cookies” or other technologies to monitor end user traffic to our web sites, we reserve the right to do so. We do not presently, but may in the future use cookies and other technologies to adjust online advertising, study traffic patterns and review the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we reserve the right to use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As is true of most web sites, especially through our online portals, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, and other data. We use this information in rendering our services. Reflected will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

10\. Commitment to Your Privacy

As we said, Reflected takes protecting your privacy seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to our employees and service providers and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. In addition, Reflected supports industry initiatives to preserve privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce.

11\. International Users

With respect to the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected from the European Union, Reflected no longer relies upon the safe harbor framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, but instead stores such information on servers located within the European Union.  Reflected’s customers also must adhere to such geographic restrictions. 

12\. Further Questions Regarding Privacy

If you have questions or concerns about Reflected’s Privacy Policy, please email [privacy@Reflected.net](mailto:privacy@Reflected.net) to contact us. Reflected will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

13\. Effective Date; Updates to Privacy Policy

The terms and conditions in this policy statement came into effect on October 1, 2015. Reflected reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy at any time and in any manner. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our web site along with the updated privacy policy. Your use of our web site and any other services provided by Reflected after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes.

14\. Notice of Compliance to California Residents

California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (“California Act”) and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the California Act, this privacy policy identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that we collect through our web site about individual consumers who use or visit our web site and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom such personally identifiable information may be shared.

Depending on the visitor’s activity at our web site, certain “personally identifiable information” (as that term is defined in the California Act) may be collected, in addition to information set forth in other sections of this document. For purposes of the California Act, the term “personally identifiable information” means individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected online by us from an individual and maintained by us in an accessible form, and may include any of the following:

(1) A first and last name;

(2) A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town;

(3) An email address;

(4) A telephone number;

(5) A social security number;

(6) Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual;

(7) Information concerning a user that the web site collects online from the user, and maintains in personally identifiable form, in combination with an identifier described within this privacy policy.

See Section 7 above entitled “Integrity of Your Personal Information” for a description of the process maintained by Reflected for an individual consumer who uses or visits our web site to review and request changes to any of his or her personally identifiable information that is collected through our web site.

See Section 13 above entitled “Effective Date; Updates to Privacy Policy” for a description of the process by which the Company notifies consumers who use or visit our web site of material changes to Reflected’s privacy policy. The effective date of this privacy policy is also included in Section 13 above.

15\. California Shine the Light Law (SB 27) Compliance Statement

Under California S.B. 27 (“Shine the Light” Law), California residents have the right under certain circumstances to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@Reflected.net](mailto:privacy@Reflected.net) and please include the phrase “California Privacy Request” in the subject line, the domain name of the web site you are inquiring about, along with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request.
